mbfinancial.com 2015-03-25

# WHAT DOES MB FINANCIAL BANK, N.A. DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

                                                                                                            Rev. 03/2013
FACTS                WHAT DOES MB FINANCIAL BANK, N.A.
                     DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell
                     you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                     carefully to understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service
                     you have with us. This information can include:
                         Social Security number and checking account information
                         Account transactions and account balances
                        Transaction history and payment history
How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                     customers’ personal information; the reasons MB Financial Bank, N.A. chooses to share;
                     and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                  Does MB Financial         Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                  Bank, N.A. share?         sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —                              Yes                       No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes —                                      Yes                       Yes
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial                          Yes                       Yes
companies
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —                  Yes                       No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —                  No                        We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                               Yes                       Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                No                        We don’t share
To limit                 Call toll free 1.888.i bank mb (1.888.422.6562) — our menu will prompt you through your
                         choice.
our sharing          Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from
                     the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share
                     your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit
                     our sharing.
Questions?               Call toll free 1.888.i bank mb (1.888.422.6562) or go to www.mbfinancial.com

Page 2
What we do
How does MB Financial           To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we
Bank, N.A. protect my           use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
personal information?           computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those
                                employees who need to know that information to provide products or
                                services to you.
How does MB Financial           We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Bank, N.A. collect my               Open an account or provide your account information.
personal information?               Apply for a loan or show us your government-issued ID.
                                    Make deposits or withdrawals from your account.
                                We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all           Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing?                            sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your
                                    creditworthiness.
                                    affiliates from using your information to market to you.
                                    sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.
                                State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit
                                sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I             Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
limit sharing for an
account I hold jointly
with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                      Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                nonfinancial companies.
                                    Our affiliates include financial service providers, such as our affiliated
                                    registered investment advisor (Cedar Hill Associates, Inc.).
Nonaffiliates                   Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                                and nonfinancial companies.
                                    MB Financial Bank, N.A. does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market
                                    to you.
Joint marketing                 A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                market financial products or services to you.
                                    Our joint marketing partners include an insurance company.
Other important information
California Residents: You do not need to contact us to limit our sharing with joint marketing partners. We will
not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to our joint marketing partners.
Vermont Residents: You do not need to contact us to limit our sharing with joint marketing partners. We will
not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to our joint marketing partners. We will not share a credit
report about you with our affiliates, except with your express consent or as permitted by law.
